{
    "unit1": [{
            "question": "√25",
            "answer": "5"
        },
        {
            "question": "3√64",
            "answer": "4"
        },
        {
            "question": "-√100",
            "answer": "-10"
        },
        {
            "question": "3√1000",
            "answer": "10"
        },
        {
            "question": "3√-27",
            "answer": "-3"
        },
        {
            "question": "√0",
            "answer": "0"
        },
        {
            "question": "√81",
            "answer": "9"
        },
        {
            "question": "3√-729",
            "answer": "-9"
        }, {
            "question": "1/2",
            "answer": "0.5"
        },
        {
            "question": "3/11",
            "answer": "0.27..."
        },
        {
            "question": "- 3/2",
            "answer": "-1.5"
        },
        {
            "question": " 6/9",
            "answer": "0.6..."
        }

    ],
    "unit2": [{
            "question": "7^2",
            "answer": "49"
        },
        {
            "question": "6^3",
            "answer": "216"
        },
        {
            "question": "-5^4",
            "answer": "625"
        },
        {
            "question": "9^0",
            "answer": "1"
        }, {
            "question": "15000000",
            "answer": "1.5*10^7"
        },
        {
            "question": "69400",
            "answer": "6.94*10^4"
        },
        {
            "question": "0.0000000000019",
            "answer": "1.9*10^-12"
        },
        {
            "question": "9.8*10^4",
            "answer": "98000"
        }, {
            "question": "362.14",
            "answer": "3.6214*10^2"
        },
        {
            "question": "0.036214",
            "answer": "3.6214*10^-2"
        }
        , {
            "question": "0.0000000153",
            "answer": "1.53*10^-8"
        },
        {
            "question": "65",
            "answer": "6.5*10^1"
        }

    ]
}